Inventory of the Colby E. "Babe" Slater Collection D-394
University of California, Davis General Library, Dept. of Special Collections
- Photographic Materials, 1906-1961; Series 5; 153 prints and 45 negatives.
  - Photographic Prints, 1906-1961; Subseries 5.1; 153 prints.
    - University of California, Davis, 1915-1961; D394.5.1.2; 28 prints. (Box 2, Folder 31-55)
      - Picnic Day "Booster Trip", 1915; D394.5.1.2.1; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 31)
        University of California, Davis -- History; Picnic Day -- History
      - Picnic Day "Welcome Arch", circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.2; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 12 cm (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Picnic Day: Children at Play, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.3; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 15 cm (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Picnic Day: Children Playing on Swings, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.4; 1 photographic print black and white 14 x 9 cm (Box 2, Folder 33A)
      - Picnic Day: Crowd Watching Parade, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.5; 1 photographic print black and white 14 x 9 cm (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Picnic Day: "Davis Band", 1916; D394.5.1.2.6; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Picnic Day: Float, Modern Farm Buildings, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.7; 1 photographic print black and white 10 x 7 cm (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Picnic Day: Float with Chickens, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.8; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 16 cm (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Picnic Day: "More Comedy", 1916; D394.5.1.2.9; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 38)
        Parade display: wagon with sheep and lambs bearing signs reading "Married 1 Year: Look What We Have", "Shropshire", and "What's Home Without a Mother".
      - Picnic Day: Horseless Carriage, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.10; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 11 cm (Box 2, Folder 39)
        Horse-drawn carriage being passed in opposite direction by "horseless carriage".
      - Picnic Day: "One of the Student Floats", 1916; D394.5.1.2.11; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 12 cm (Box 2, Folder 40)
        Float with student on wagon hoeing crops.
      - Picnic Day: Wagon with Livestock, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.12; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Picnic Day: Wagon with Livestock, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.13; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 16 cm (Box 2, Folder 41A)
        Same image as 2:41
      - Picnic Day: Tractor and Float, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.14; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 15 cm (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Picnic Day: Tractor and Float, Side View, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.15; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 11 cm (Box 2, Folder 42A)
      - Picnic Day: "Floats on Exhibition", circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.16; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 16 cm (Box 2, Folder 43)
        "The floats are on exhibition after the parade."
      - Picnic Day: Refreshment Stand, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.17; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Picnic Day: "Lunch", 1916; D394.5.1.2.18; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Picnic Day: "A Little Parking Space", 1916; D394.5.1.2.19; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 46)
        Automobiles parked in field.
      - [Picnic Day?]: Crowd on Bleachers, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.20; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Picnic Day: Grand Champion Steer of 1916 International, D394.5.1.2.21; 1 photographic print sepia 16 x 21 cm (Box 2, Folder 48)
        "California Favorite. Grand Champion Steer of 1916 International. Bred, fed, and exhibited by the University of California Farm, Davis, Cal. Sold for the Worlds record price of $1.75 per lb."
      - Baseball Game, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.22; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 49)
        College sports -- California -- Davis; University of California, Davis -- History
      - Animal Husbandry Building, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.23; 1 photographic print sepia 9 x 12 cm (Box 2, Folder 50)
        University of California, Davis -- History; University of California, Davis. Department of Animal Husbandry -- Pictorial works
      - Calpha Fraternity House, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.24; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 11 cm (Box 2, Folder 51)
        Greek letter societies -- California -- Davis; University of California, Davis -- History; University of California, Davis -- Students -- Societies, etc
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, circa 1916; D394.5.1.2.25; 1 photographic print sepia 15 x 9 cm; 1 photographic print sepia 27 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 52, Folder 86)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, circa 1917; D394.5.1.2.26; 1 photographic print black and white 10 x 7 cm (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Cal Aggie Alumni Association, 1957; D394.5.1.2.27; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 17 cm; 5 leaves, 1 envelope 8.5 x 11 inches, 5.5 x 8.5 inches (Box 2, Folder 53A)
        "Block CA Alumni Committee, July 6, 1957. Top Row: Babe Slater, Chet Locke, Joe Fiack, Will [Lotter?], Bill Harper. Bottom Row: Jack Underhill, Dean DeCarli, Crip Toomey, Ralph Moss."
        Includes letter from Cal Aggie Alumni Association Class of 1917 Committee and list of members of class of 1917.
        California Aggie Alumni Association; Block CA Society; Slater, Colby E.
      - College of Agriculture Exhibit, Junior Livestock Show, March 1961; D394.5.1.2.28; 1 photographic print black and white 21 x 26 cm (Box 2, Folder 54)
        Agricultural exhibitions; University of California (1868-1952). College of Agriculture
      - Alumni on Picnic Day, April 1961; D394.5.1.2.29; 1 photographic print black and white 21 x 26 cm (Box 2, Folder 55)
        Note on verso: "Babe - Sorry I blocked you out."
        Explanatory note by Marilyn Slater McCapes: "[Left] John Rodger. [Right] Bob Lockhart: Dad's best friend and school chum and farmed with Dad. Went to work for Bank of America. Dad is behind Lockhart and partially blocked."
        Slater, Colby E.; Picnic Day -- History
      - (Babe) Slater Perpetual Athletic Trophy, 23 October 1965; D394.5.1.2.30; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 55A)
        "Herb Barker - left. Carol Hahn, Acting Vice President Student Body. Jim Tavernetti. Babe Slater Perpetual Athletic Trophy. Aggie-Chico State game."
        UC Davis Athletics -- History; University of California, Davis -- Sports
    - World War I, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3; 28 photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 56-74)
      - Four Soldiers and a Boy, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.1; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 56)
        World War, 1914-1918; Soldiers -- Pictorial works
      - Four Soldiers and a Woman, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.2; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Four Soldiers, Seated, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.3; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Four Soldiers Wearing Gas Masks, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.4; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - Four Soldiers With Shaved Heads, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.5; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - Six Soldiers, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.6; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 61)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater and Other Soldiers by Building, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.7; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 8 cm (Box 2, Folder 62)
        World War, 1914-1918; Soldiers -- Pictorial works; Slater, Colby E.
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater in Snow, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.8; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 9 cm (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Soldier and Man (Not in Uniform), circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.9; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 5 cm (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - Soldier by Stable, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.10; 1 photographic print sepia 7 x 5 cm (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - Soldier Standing in Snow, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.11; 1 photographic print sepia 8 x 5 cm (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Soldier with Bed Roll, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.12; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 6 cm (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Soldiers at Camp, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.13; 1 photographic print sepia 5 x 8 cm (Box 2, Folder 68.1)
        Company at parade grounds.
      - Soldiers at Camp, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.14; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 2, Folder 68.2)
        Company at barracks
      - Five Soldiers at Camp, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.15; 1 photographic print sepia 5 x 7 cm (Box 2, Folder 68.3)
      - View of Camp, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.16; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 2, Folder 68.4)
        World War, 1914-1918
      - Two Soldiers at Camp, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.17; 1 photographic print sepia 8 x 5 cm (Box 2, Folder 68.5)
      - Soldiers at Railyard, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.18; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 69.1)
      - Soldiers at Railyard: View of Train, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.19; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 69.2)
      - Soldier by Building, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.20; 1 photographic print sepia 8 x 6 cm (Box 2, Folder 70.1)
        Portrait of man facing camera
      - Seven Soldiers by Building, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.21; 1 photographic print sepia 5 x 7 cm (Box 2, Folder 70.2)
        Men posed for group photograph
      - Soldier by Building, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.22; 1 photographic print sepia 8 x 6 cm (Box 2, Folder 70.3)
        Portrait of man turned partly away from camera
      - Soldier by Building, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.23; 1 photographic print sepia 7 x 5 cm (Box 2, Folder 70.4)
        Portrait of soldier with moustache
      - Soldiers in Barracks, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.24; 1 photographic print black and white 14 x 8 cm (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - Soldiers on Horseback, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.25; 1 photographic print sepia 8 x 5 cm (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - Three Soldiers and a Woman, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.26; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Two Soldiers Bathing in Sea, circa 1918; D394.5.1.3.27; 1 photographic print black and white 14 x 8 cm (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Seventh Olympic Games, Antwerp, Belgium, 1920; D394.5.1.4; 11 prints (Box 2, Folder 75-84, Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Rugby Match: United States versus Unidentified Team, 1920; D394.5.1.4.1; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 75)
        Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team Group Portrait, 1920; D394.5.1.4.2; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 11 cm (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team Official (?) Group Portrait, 1920; D394.5.1.4.3; 2 photographic prints black and white 12 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 77)
        "American Rugby Team, Olympic Winners, 1920."
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team on Tour of France: United States versus Sud-Ouest at Bordeaux, October 1920; D394.5.1.4.4; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team on Tour of France: United States versus Sud-Ouest at Bordeaux. Players in scrum, October 1920; D394.5.1.4.5; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team on Tour of France: United States versus Sud-Ouest at Bordeaux. Players in scrum, October 1920; D394.5.1.4.6; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 80)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team on Tour of France: United States versus Sud-Ouest at Bordeaux. Players during tackle, October 1920; D394.5.1.4.7; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 81)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team on Tour of France: United States versus Sud-Ouest at Bordeaux. Players after tackle, October 1920; D394.5.1.4.8; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 82)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team on Tour of France: United States versus Sud-Ouest at Bordeaux. Players on field during match, October 1920; D394.5.1.4.9; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 2, Folder 83)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team on Tour of France: United States versus Sud-Ouest at Bordeaux. Players in scrum, October 1920; D394.5.1.4.10; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm; Photograph is damaged. (Box 2, Folder 84)
      - Photograph of rugby team including Slater (possibly 1920 Olympic Team), D394.5.1.4.11; 1 photographic print black and white 36 x 23 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
        L.R. 1. Jim Wiley 2. Carroll 3. G. Hunter 4. ? 5. Doe 6. Slater 7. Davis 8. Winston 9. J. Muldoon 10. Fitzpatrick 11. Wallace 12. Tilden 13. Bill Muldoon 14. Wrenn 15. Meehan.
        Rugby football teams -- United States; Rugby football
    - Eighth Olympic Games, Paris, 1924-1925; D394.5.1.5; 22 prints. (Box 3, Folder 1-16, Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater in Practice Sweater, March 1924; D394.5.1.5.1; 2 photographic prints 3 x 4 inches (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Colby E. Slater's Passport, March 27, 1924; D394.5.1.5.2; 1 volume 31 x 42 cm (16 x 12 cm folded) (Box 3, Folder 2.1)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, 1924; D394.5.1.5.3; 1 photographic print 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 2.2)
        Identical print of photo found in his 1924 Passport.
        Slater, Colby E.; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
      - United States Olympic Rugby team member Colby E. "Babe" Slater aboard ship, 1924; D394.5.1.5.4; 1 photographic print 8 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team aboard ship, 1924; D394.5.1.5.5; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 11 cm (Box 3, Folder 4.1)
        Note
        Group shot on deck of ship. Slater is standing in the far left of the middle row.
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team aboard ship, 1924; D394.5.1.5.6; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 11 cm (Box 3, Folder 4.2)
        Group shot of team on board a ship. Slater is standing (legs crossed) on the far left of the middle row.
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team member changes into uniform on deck of ship, 1924; D394.5.1.5.7; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 5.1)
        Rugby football teams -- United States; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
      - Four members of United States Olympic Rugby Team on deck of ship, 1924; D394.5.1.5.8; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 5.2)
      - Three members of the United States Olympic Rugby Team on deck of ship, 1924; d394.5.1.5.9; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
        From left to right: Al Williams, Unidentified, Linn Farrish.
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team members John Cunningham and William "Lefty" Rogers on deck of ship, 1924; D394.5.1.5.10; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Two United States Olympic Rugby Team members?, 1924; D394.5.1.5.11; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team member Rudolph "Rudy" Scholz standing in front of Patzenhofer Bier-Hallen, circa 1924; D394.5.1.5.12; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team member Al Valentine, 1924; D394.5.1.5.13; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
        Rugby football teams -- United States; Rugby football; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team members Al Williams, Colby "Babe" Slater, Linn Farish, [undentified], 1924; D394.5.1.5.14; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 15 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Rugby match (or practice?), 1924; D394.5.1.5.15; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - United States Olympic Rugby Team with Mme Luella Melius, 1924; D394.5.1.5.16; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
        L'equipe americaine de rugby recoit "Cali" La poupée mascotte des mains de Mme Luella Melius. CL C.O.F. 850
      - Postcard of California Olympic Rugby Team in British Columbia, 1925; D394.5.1.5.17; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 14 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
        2 copies of postcard.
      - California Olympic Rugby Team at Brockton Point, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1925; D394.5.1.5.18; 1 photographic print black and white 19 x 24 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
        "California Olympic Rugby Team, 1925. Brockton Point, Vancouver B.C." Front row (left-right): Jim Kelly, Caesar Manelli, Geo. Skinner, Geo. Colley, Charlie Doe (Captain), Charlie Grandona, R. Scholly, Eddie Graf, F. Klein. Back row (left-right): Al Williams, Swede Leistner, J. Cashel, P. Clark, Dink. Templeton, Morris Kirksey, J. Hannan, L. Farish, G. Hunter, J. Wylie, C. Dodge, "Babe" Slater, Harry Maloney (Manager).
      - Postcard of The Lions and Burrard Inlet, Vancouver, British Columbia, undated; D394.5.1.5.19; 1 photographic print black and white 14 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
        "Published by The Coast Publishing Co., Vancouver, B.C."
        Vancouver (B.C.)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, Al Williams, and Rene Lasserre, 1924; D394.5.1.5.20; 1 photographic print black and white 26 x 35 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
        Left to right: Slater (U.S. Team Captain), Al Williams (U.S. Coach), Rene Lasserre (French Team Captain)
    - Family and Friends, 1906-1961; D394.5.1.6; 27 photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 17-36)
      - Marguerite Slater Messenger, circa 1918; D394.5.1.6.1; 1 photographic print sepia 27 x 17 cm (Box 2, Folder 85)
        Sister of Colby E. "Babe" Slater
        Messenger, Marguerite Slater; Slater family
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, circa 1913; D394.5.1.6.37; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 27 cm (Box 2, Folder 86)
      - Slater family at house on Shattuck Avenue, Berkeley, California, circa 1906; D394.5.1.6.2; 1 photographic print black and white 14 x 18 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
        copyprint
        From Left to right: Minnie White?, Henry Boone, Captain William Colby, Louise Slater, Bruce(?), Hannah McDonald, Margaret Shannahan Chenery Colby, Marguerite Slater, Norman Slater, Colby "Babe" Slater.
        Slater, Colby E.; Slater family; Messenger, Marguerite Slater; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979
      - Five boys, 1910; D394.5.1.6.3; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 11 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Left to right: Colby E. "Babe" Slater, unidentified, Norman Slater, unidentified, unidentified.
        Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater with friends, circa 1918; d394.5.1.6.4; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, mother Louise, and brother Norman, circa 1924; d394.5.1.6.5; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 15 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
        Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979; Slater family
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater camping with the Lawlor family on the North Coast, prior to 1932; D394.5.1.6.6; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 12 cm (Box 3, Folder 21.1)
        Left to right: Slater (seated on log eating a banana) and four Lawlor family members on a beach.
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater sitting on log on a North Coast beach smoking a pipe, prior to 1932; D394.5.1.6.7; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 21.2)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater sitting on log with unidentified girl on a North Coast Beach, prior to 1932; D394.5.1.6.8; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 21.3)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater with baby daughter, Marilyn, circa 1934; D394.5.1.6.9; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Virginia C. Slater (and others) sitting at a banquet table at the Palace Hotel, San Francisco, California, March 22, 1947; D394.5.1.6.10; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 18 cm (Box 3, Folder 22A.1)
        Image taken during the University of California Alumni Association's 79th Annual Charter Baquet, held at the Palm Court Palace Hotel, San Francsico, March 22, 1947.
        Slater, Virgina C., 1909-1991
      - Program from the University of California Alumni Association's Seventy-ninth Annual Charter Banquet, Palm Court Palace Hotel, Saturday March 22, 1947, D394.5.1.6.11; 1 program color illustrations 28 cm (folded) (Box 3, Folder 22A.3)
        Notes
        Contains the banquent table layout and the names of attendees.
        California Alumnni Association
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, January 1952; D394.5.1.6.12; 1 photographic print black and white 18 x 13 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, January 1952; D394.5.1.6.13; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Virginia C. Slater, 1952; D394.5.1.6.14; 1 photographic print black and white 18 x 13 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater and Virginia C. Slater passport photo, 1954; D394.5.1.6.15; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 25A)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, February 10, 1959; D394.5.1.6.16; 1 photographic print black and white 11 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
        Polaroid print.
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater and Virginia C. Slater, circa 1960; D394.5.1.6.17; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 27.1)
        Photograph taken for visas.
      - Virginia C. Slater, circa 1960; D394.5.1.6.18; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 27.2)
        Photograph taken for visa.
      - Colby E. Slater, circa 1960; D394.5.1.6.19; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 27.3)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater and Norman Slater, Jr. (Babe's nephew), March 1961; D394.5.1.6.20; 1 photographic print black and white 21 x 26 cm (Box 3, Folder 28)
        Farm equipment; Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B., Jr., 1919-2013
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater on his Clarksburg, California farm, March 1961; D394.5.1.6.21; 1 photographic print black and white 22 x 28 cm (Box 3, Folder 29.1)
        Farmers -- California -- Yolo County.; Agriculture -- California -- Yolo County; Slater, Colby E.
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater on his Clarksburg, California farm, March 1961; D394.5.1.6.22; 1 photographic print black and white 13 x 17 cm (Box 3, Folder 29.2)
        Agriculture -- California -- Yolo County; Farmers -- California -- Yolo County.; Slater, Colby E.
      - Norman Slater, Jr. (Babe's nephew), March 1961; D394.5.1.6.23; 1 photographic print black and white 21 x 26 cm (Box 3, Folder 29A)
        Farm equipment; Slater, Norman B., Jr., 1919-2013
      - Carolyn Jensen (Babe's granddaughter) kneeling next to Slater's plaque on the Rugby Pathway of Fame, Rugby, Warwickshire, United Kingdom, September 25, 2004; D394.85.1.6.24; 1 photographic print color 13 x 17 cm (Box 3, Folder 29B.1)
        Rugby football; Slater, Colby E.
      - Carolyn Jensen (Babe's granddaughter) kneeling next to Slater's plaque on the Rugby Pathway of Fame, Rugby, Warwickshire, United Kingdom, September 25, 2004; D394.5.1.6.25; 1 photographic print color 18 x 13 cm (Box 3, Folder 29B.2)
      - Slater's plaque on the Rugby Pathway of Fame, Rugby, Warwickshire, United Kingdom, September 25, 2004; D394.5.1.6.26; 1 photographic print color 13 x 18 cm (Box 3, Folder 29B.2)
        3 prints.
      - Lodge at Twain Harte, California?, undated; D394.5.1.6.27; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 30)